Guide to the Cookie Teer Papers, 1971-2000, bulk 1983-1997 RL.01282
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Subject Files Series, 1971-2000, 37 boxes
  - Illinois and Maryland Commission for Women (Box 12)
  - Indianapolis – ordinance, newspaper articles pertaining to (Box 12)
  - Indianapolis – appeal, 1985, 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Indianapolis – decisions, 1984-1985 (Box 12)
  - Indianapolis – law, 1985 (Box 12)
  - Indianapolis – ordinance, 1984-1985 (Box 12)
  - Indianapolis briefs, 1984-1985, 3 folders (Box 13)
  - Infanticide, 1986 (Box 13)
  - Jaggar, Alison (Box 13)
  - Johnson, Sonia (Box 13)
  - Jolly, Dawn, 1990 (Box 13)
  - Jones, Beverly (Box 13)
  - Jordan, Milton (Box 13)
  - Juvenile Law Study Commission – Paul Stam (Box 13)
  - Juvenile Law Study, N.C. – Paul Stam – sadistic video, statutory rape (Box 13)
  - Kaplan, Temma (Box 13)
  - Kasl – women and sex addiction (Box 13)
  - Kilbourne – resources for change bibliography (Box 13)
  - Lahey, Kathleen (Box 13)
  - Langer, Phyllis (Box 13)
  - Language, sexist (Box 13)
  - Lederer, Laura (Box 13)
  - Legitimate bookstore industry (Box 13)
  - Leidholdt, Dorchen (Box 13)
  - Lesbian - GiRLFRIENDS Magazine (Box 13)
  - Lesbian/gay rights, Durham, N.C. (Box 13)
  - Letters/drafts and correspondence (Box 13)
  - Letters to editors, 1985 Feb.-Dec. (Box 14)
  - Letters to editors, 1986 Jan.-Aug. (Box 14)
  - Letters to editors, 1984-1986 (Box 14)
  - Linz – liability and legal – research used for legal change, 1982 (Box 14)
  - Linz – liability and legal – "Bases of liability for injuries produced by media portrayals of violent porn," 1983 (Box 14)
  - Liptzin, Dr. Myron B., 1986 (Box 14)
  - Lipton, Morris, 1985 (Box 14)
  - Looking, 1986 (Box 14)
  - Los Angeles ordinance, 1985 (Box 14)
  - Los Angeles Council on Women hearing (Box 14)
  - Malamuth, Neil – "Pornography and Sexual Aggression" (Box 14)
  - Malamuth, Neil – violence in erotica (Box 14)
  - Mail order porn, 1986 (Box 14)
  - Mail order brides, 1986-1988 (Box 14)
  - "A Male Grief" – porn and addiction (Box 14)
  - Male – sex needs, hormones, 1991 (Box 14)
  - Marital rape, 1982-1995, 2 folders (Box 14)
  - Marriage and divorce, 1988-1996 (Box 14)
  - Marriage and divorce statistics (Box 14)
  - Marshall, Pam (Box 14)
  - Marchiano, Linda Lovelace, 1984-1987 (Box 14)
  - Maryland Commission for Women, 1984 (Box 15)
  - Media contacts (Box 15)
  - Media violence – ZAP, advertising, 1983-1986 (Box 15)
  - Media violence – censorship and cable TV, 1990 (Box 15)
  - Media violence – general, 1984-1990 (Box 15)
  - Media violence – music, 1984-1990 (Box 15)
  - Media violence – television, 1988 (Box 15)
  - Media violence – Violence Against Women in Media, Maryland Commission for Women, 1984 (Box 15)
  - Media violence – Brown, Jane, videos, 1986-1991 (Box 15)
  - Media violence – sport, 1985-1991 (Box 15)
  - Melrose, Julie, 1985 (Box 15)
  - Men's rights, 1986-1990 (Box 15)
  - Men's rights – odd, 1983-1986 (Box 15)
  - Mental health – DSM-III-R and mental health professionals (Box 15)
  - Model anti-pornography law (Box 15)
  - Minneapolis ordinance – city – Tribe letter (Box 15)
  - Minneapolis ordinance, 1983 and 1987 (Box 15)
  - Minneapolis civil rights ordinance, 1985-1986 (Box 15)
  - Minneapolis press coverage, 1983-1992 (Box 15)
  - Minneapolis – Van White, pro-CR ordinance, 1984 (Box 15)
  - Minneapolis – questions on ordinance (Box 15)
  - Materials on anti-pornography civil rights ordinances, 1985 (Box 15)
  - Montgomery, Bibba, 1986 (Box 15)
  - Moore, Jamie (Box 15)
  - Money, John (Johns Hopkins), 1986-1990 (Box 15)
  - Morgan, Robin, 1989 April (Box 15)
  - MADD (Box 15)
  - Mother Jones, 1980-1986 (Box 15)
  - Mother Jones – Jeffrey Masson, 1984-1987 (Box 15)
  - Ms. Magazine – letters and clippings, 1987 (Box 16)
  - Ms. Magazine (Box 16)
  - Myth N.C., 1985 (Box 16)
  - MacKinnon, Catherine, 1989-1994 (Box 16)
  - MacKinnon brief – Black Women's Health Project – hate speech, 1991 Oct. (Box 16)
  - MacKinnon – letters to OOB, Adrienne Rich, 1985 (Box 16)
  - MacKinnon – C.V. (Box 16)
  - MacKinnon – Donnerstein phone conversation, 1984 Jan. 10 (Box 16)
  - MacKinnon – feminism, Marxism, ERA, etc. (Box 16)
  - MacKinnon – miscellaneous, 1982-1983 (Box 16)
  - MacKinnon – feminist critique, "Not a moral issue" (Box 16)
  - MacKinnon – "Pleasure under patriarchy" (Box 16)
  - MacKinnon – Roe v. Wade (Box 16)
  - MacKinnon – Village Voice (Box 16)
  - MacKinnon – Michigan, 1989-1990 (Box 16)
  - MacKinnon – Pornography and Civil Rights, 1988 (Box 16)
  - MacKinnon, McIntyre – Women and Law, 1986 (Box 16)
  - "Masterpieces," 1984 (Box 16)
  - McCombs, Annie, 1986-1996, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - McIntyre, Sheila, 1986 Mar. 22 (Box 17)
  - McNamara, Suzanne, 1986-1987 (Box 17)
  - Matsuda, Mari, 1989 Aug. (Box 17)
  - Nakell, Barry, 1991 and 1997 (Box 17)
  - NAPCRO – Steve Jevning – national civil rights anti-porn ordinance, 1985-1988, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - NAPCRO grants (Box 17)
  - National Black Women's Health Project, 1989 (Box 17)
  - National Coalition Against Pornography, 1986 (Box 17)
  - National Coalition Against Pornography – Jerry Kirk (Box 17)
  - National Center for Prevention and Control of Rape, 1981-1993 (Box 17)
  - National Coalition on Television Violence, 1987-1990 (Box 17)
  - National Federation for Decency, 1986 (Box 17)
  - Newsletters from various organizations, 1986-1988 (Box 17)
  - National Organization for Women (NOW), 1985-1991, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - NOW – porn, N.C. NOW, 1984-1986 (Box 18)
  - NOW Task Force on Violence Against Women, 1985 (Box 18)
  - N.C. NOW, 1985-1987 (Box 18)
  - N.C. NOW conference, 1985 Sept. – Nikki – resolution, DFT – Task Force – resolution (Box 18)
  - NOW hearings on pornography, 1985-1986 (Box 18)
  - National NOW resolution on porn and prostitution, 1985-1986 (Box 18)
  - NOW National Conference, 1986 June 13-15 (Box 18)
  - National NOW Conference, 1985 (Box 18)
  - Chapel Hill NOW bylaws, 1982, 1986-1987 (Box 18)
  - NOW hearings on porn and NOW opposition, 1986-1987 (Box 18)
  - NOW – articles about pornography, letters to NOW about pornography, 1985-1989 (Box 18)
  - NOW Legal Defense Fund, 1986-1992 (Box 18)
  - NOW – E.R.A. and Constitution facts and dates, 1974-1989 (Box 18)
  - NAMBLA, 1986 Nov. (Box 19)
  - Texas NOW, 1986 (Box 19)
  - NC Council on the Status of Women, 1986-1988 (Box 19)
  - New Right/Religion, 1987-1989 (Box 19)
  - NY State Council of Churches (Box 19)
  - NY State Council of Churches – PREAP, 1985 (Box 19)
  - NC child abuse laws, 1986 (Box 19)
  - NC child abuse studies, 1987 (Box 19)
  - NC child abuse survey, 1999 (Box 19)
  - NC crime statistics, 1987-1998 (Box 19)
  - NC debate on pornography, 1985-1986 (Box 19)
  - NC Equity, 1988-1990 (Box 19)
  - NC Legislature, 1983-1984, 1987 (Box 19)
  - NC obscenity law on libraries, 1986 June 21 (Box 19)
  - NC – "new" obscenity law, 1985-1987 (Box 19)
  - NC obscenity law, definitions, 1984-1991 (Box 19)
  - NC state and local politics, 1986-1988 (Box 19)
  - NC politicians, 1986-1988 (Box 19)
  - NC Victim Assistance Network and Child Victimization Resource Center, 1985-1989 (Box 19)
  - NC victims legislation, 1986-1988 (Box 19)
  - Newspaper – addresses (Box 19)
  - Newsweek porn war, 1985 Mar. (Box 19)
  - Northampton – Lierre and Dorian, 1988-1992 (Box 19)
  - Non-sexist guidelines, 1985 (Box 20)
  - Not a Love Story, 1985 (Box 20)
  - O'Barr, Jean (Signs), 1988 (Box 20)
  - Obscene phone calls, 1990 (Box 20)
  - Obscenity law – prosecutions and arrests, 1986-1987 (Box 20)
  - Obscenity law harmful to minors, 1986-1988 (Box 20)
  - Obscenity law, other countries, Turkey, 1988 Mar. 23 (Box 20)
  - Obscenity N.C., 1983, 2 folders (Box 20)
  - Obscenity – miscellaneous, 1992 (Box 20)
  - Obscenity report, 1984 March 9 (Box 20)
  - Obscenity commentary, 1980-1987 (Box 20)
  - Off Our Backs, 1985 Feb.-July (Box 20)
  - Off Our Backs – letters, 1985 (Box 20)
  - Off Our Backs – ordinance, 1985 (Box 20)
  - Off Our Backs pornography ordinance debate, 1985 (Box 20)
  - Olsen, Fran (Box 20)
  - Opposition – Brownmiller, Harper's, 1984 Nov. (Box 20)
  - Opposition – DeCrow, Betty Friedan, 1985 (See also: Penthouse) (Box 20)
  - Opposition – on DePalma, 1984-1985 (Box 20)
  - Opposition – F.A.C.T. writing, 1984-1985 (Box 20)
  - Opposition – F.A.C.T. press coverage, 1985 (Box 20)
  - Opposition – GC News, 1984 May 19 (Box 20)
  - Opposition – Trivia, 1985 (Box 20)
  - Opposition – The Humanist, 1985 (Box 20)
  - Opposition – miscellaneous, 1986-1995 (Box 20)
  - Opposition – Penthouse (See also: DeCrow) (Box 20)
  - Opposition – The Sun, John Rosenthal (Box 20)
  - Opposition – S/M (Califia), 1985-1986 (Box 20)
  - Opposition, 1990-1996 (Box 20)
  - Orange County Democratic Party (Box 20)
  - Orange County women, 1997 Apr. 13 (Box 20)
  - O.A.P. – Organizing Against Pornography, 1987-1995 (Box 21)
  - Osanka, Frank, 1988-1991 (Box 21)
  - Orange County HRC – hearings, 1989 (Box 21)
  - Orange County HRC – ORD, 1990 Dec. 8 (Box 21)
  - Orange County HRC – CA Hate Crimes Bill AB.239, 1989 (Box 21)
  - HRC – Orange County, 1988-1989 (Box 21)
  - Orange County HRC – battered women news clips, 1988-1990 (Box 21)
  - Orange County – Jolly, Dawn, 1989 (Box 21)
  - Orange County HRC – justice for women speech, vigil (Box 21)
  - Racism hearing, HRC, 1989 May 31 (Box 21)
  - Orange County HRC – housing, 1990 Jan. 25 (Box 21)
  - Orange County HRC – Klan rally, 1988 Apr. 30 (Box 21)
  - Joyce Green's paper – KKK, 1987 Dec. (Box 21)
  - Alan McSurely's paper – KKK (Box 21)
  - Orange County HRC – gay/lesbian hearing, 1989 Apr. 13 (Box 21)
  - Orange County HRC – Orange County Civil Rights Ordinance, 1992 (Box 21)
  - Orange County HRC news clips, 1988-1990 (Box 21)
  - Orange County HRC – related news clips, 1988-1989 (Box 21)
  - Orange County custody study, 1991 (Box 21)
  - Orange County Commission on Women – "Rape: The Practice of the Sexual," 1989 (Box 21)
  - Orange County Rape Crisis Center, 1984-1989 (Box 21)
  - Orange County violence stats, 1990-1991 (Box 21)
  - Orange County custody, rape – miscellaneous, 1980-1999 (Box 22)
  - Orange County Commission for Women conference, 1989 (Box 22)
  - Painted Witch, 1985 (Box 22)
  - Penthouse, 1983-1991, 3 folders (Box 22)
  - Penthouse – Charity Snider (Box 22)
  - "Pieces" demonstration, 1984 Jan. 26 (Box 22)
  - Playboy, 1973-1996, 2 folders (Box 22)
  - Porn and black women, 1990 Feb. 27 (Box 22)
  - Porn industry – Playboy advisor statistic, 1986 (Box 22)
  - Playboy – Stratten vs. Heffner, 1985 (Box 22)
  - Politically correct, 1991 (Box 22)
  - Pornography – press (Box 22)
  - Pornography and Civil Rights – Dworkin and MacKinnon – draft, 1987 (Box 22)
  - Pornography Awareness interviews and articles, 1985 Jan.-June (Box 22)
  - Pornography Awareness interviews and articles, 1985 June-Dec. (Box 22)
  - Pornography Awareness interviews and articles, 1984-1985 Jan. (Box 23)
  - Pornography Awareness interviews and articles, 1986 (Box 23)
  - Pornography Awareness – photographs (Box 23)
  - Pornography Awareness slideshow, 1989 Dec. (Box 23)
  - Pornography Awareness slideshow, 1989 Dec. – clean copy (Box 23)
  - Pornography Awareness articles, CHN – Richard Burnett (Box 23)
  - Pornography Awareness organization, 2 folders (Box 23)
  - Pornography Awareness – IRS, 1985-1993 (Box 23)
  - Pornography Awareness petition (Box 23)
  - Pornography Awareness newsletter (Box 23)
  - Pornography Awareness talks, 1988-1992 (Box 23)
  - Pornography Awareness schedules/events, 1985-1986 (See also: Cookie talks) (Box 23)
  - Pornography Awareness talks – N.C. NOW workshop, Greenville – homophobia, Kiwanis, human rights (Box 23)
  - Pornography Awareness – talks on ordinance (Box 23)
  - Pornography Awareness sexual harassment workshop, 1987 Aug. (Box 23)
  - Porn bibliography (Box 23)
  - Pornography Awareness talks and correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Pornography Awareness talks and correspondence, 1986 (Box 23)
  - Pornography Awareness talks and correspondence, 1985-1990 (Box 23)
  - Pornography Awareness letters – correspondence, general, 1983-1987 (Box 24)
  - Pornography Awareness unanswered correspondence, 1986-1990 (Box 24)
  - Pettigrew, Lorelee, 1985 Sept. 24 (Box 24)
  - Pornography workshop, 1990 (Box 24)
  - Phone sex (Box 24)
  - Pornography workshop proposal – Texas Council on Family Violence, 1986 June 30 (Box 24)
  - Porn bibliography (Box 24)
  - Porn info – International Networks group (Box 24)
  - Porn industry – "Indecent Exposure" (Box 24)
  - Porn industry – general articles, 1982-1988 (Box 24)
  - Porn industry – anti (against) porno, 1985-1987 (Box 24)
  - Porn industry – women's erotica?/porn, 1985-1987 (Box 24)
  - Porn industry – porno on campus, 1986 (Box 24)
  - Porn industry – models, 1984-1985 (Box 24)
  - Porn industry – perpetrators, 1985-1988 (Box 24)
  - Porn industry – organized crime and porno, 1986 (Box 24)
  - Porn industry – porno zones, 1988 (Box 24)
  - Porn industry, 1988-1993 (Box 24)
  - Pornography – child porno perpetrators in N.C., 1987 (Box 24)
  - Pornography – children and porn (Box 24)
  - Pornography – college bookstores, 1982-1994 (Box 24)
  - Pornography on campus, 1986-1988 (Box 24)
  - Pornography – male art, 1988 May 27 (Box 24)
  - Pornography, political economy of, 1981 (Box 24)
  - Porn/pregnancy, 1991 (Box 24)
  - Pornography – public attitude toward (survey), 1986-1987 (Box 24)
  - Pornography and sex crimes, 1986-1987 (Box 24)
  - Pornography and sexual abuse of women, 1984-1985 (Box 24)
  - Pornography – trials, 1986-1998 (Box 24)
  - Pornography – victims, 1986-1989 (Box 24)
  - Pornography – victims bill, 1987 Feb. 24 (Box 24)
  - Pornography and violent crime, 1984-1988 (Box 24)
  - Pornography – miscellaneous, 1987-1991 (Box 24)
  - Pornography – media, 1991 Sept. 20 (Box 24)
  - Pornography – media, ads, 1984-1988 (Box 24)
  - Pornography – media, films (movies), 1986-1987 (Box 24)
  - Pornography – media, magazines (and sales in stores), 1985-1988 (See Also: Penthouse, Playboy, and Hustler) (Box 24)
  - Pornography – media, mail order, 1986-1988 (Box 24)
  - Pornography – media, music, rock, porno rock, 1987-1988 (Box 25)
  - Pornography – media, phone sex (dial-a-porn), 1987-1989 (Box 25)
  - Pornography – video, VCRs, 1986-1996 (Box 25)
  - Pornography – video games, 1988-1995 (Box 25)
  - Pornography – Asian, 1986-1990 (Box 25)
  - Pornography – Brazil, Canada, 1987-1988 (Box 25)
  - Pornography – Ethiopia (Box 25)
  - Pornography – Sweden, 1985 (Box 25)
  - Pornography Victims Protection Act, 1988 (Box 25)
  - Pornography Resource Center (Box 25)
  - Pornography Resource Center – incorporation, 1984 (Box 25)
  - Pornography Resource Center – racism, 1983-1984 (Box 25)
  - Pornography Resource Center – resource (Box 25)
  - Pornography Resource Center sample grants, 1984-1985 (Box 25)
  - Poverty – employment, 1986-1990 (Box 25)
  - Prostitution in Durham and N.C., 1985-1992 (Box 25)
  - Orange County – Gayle Trauco, 1990 (Box 25)
  - Prostitution, 1984-1993, 2 folders (Box 25)
  - Prostitution – college students, 1986-1987 (Box 25)
  - Prostitution – massage parlor health clubs, 1988 (Box 25)
  - Prostitution – Canada Pornography and Prostitution Report (Box 25)
  - Domestic violence resources – Orange-Durham Coalition for Battered Women, 1990 (Box 25)
  - Domestic violence resources – Handbook of Federal Resources on Domestic Violence, 1980 Dec. (Box 25)
  - Domestic violence resources – In Our Best Interest, 1987, and others (Box 26)
  - Race, 1982-1991 (Box 26)
  - Race – Black, 1985-1991 (Box 26)
  - Race – Black women, pornography, "pride," 1984-1990 (Box 26)
  - Race – Black women and harm in pornography (Box 26)
  - Race – Black male and female relations, 1984 June (Box 26)
  - Race – White supremacists, 1985-1987 (Box 26)
  - Rainbow Lobby/ L. Fulani, 1990 (Box 26)
  - Psychiatrist – Bressler, B., 1986-1988 (Box 26)
  - Pullen, Carol, 1989-1990 (Box 26)
  - Rape crises for Blacks, 1985-1986 (Box 26)
  - Rape crisis centers, national (Box 26)
  - NC rape protocol, 1996-1997 (Box 26)
  - Rape – violent crime, gang rape, 1983-1986 (Box 26)
  - NC rape law, 1987-1997 (Box 26)
  - Rape – violent crime, journal articles, 1984-1991 (Box 26)
  - Stop rape, 1988 Sept. 19 (Box 26)
  - Rape – violent crime, New Bedford, 1983 (Box 26)
  - Rape – violence, cultural perception of male violence, 1988-1999 (Box 26)
  - Rape – Confronting Rape Culture – Duke women's conference, 1989 Apr. 6-8 (Box 26)
  - Rape – violence against women students, 1986-1990 (Box 26)
  - Rape, 1983-1999 (Box 26)
  - Rape victims, 1986-1998 (Box 26)
  - Rape victims and law, 1985-1988 (Box 26)
  - KKK – racism/sexism, 1986-1999 (Box 26)
  - KKK – race issues, 1995 Oct. 30 (Box 26)
  - KKK, 1986-1991 (Box 26)
  - Raymond, Jan, 1986-1989 (Box 27)
  - Reilly, C.J., correspondence, 1986 (Box 27)
  - Reisman, Judith, 1981-1987 (3 folders) (Box 27)
  - Reproductive technology, 1986-1991 (Box 27)
  - Reproductive technology – surrogate mothers, 1985-1991 (Box 27)
  - Review essays, 1984-1986 (Box 27)
  - Ritual abuse, 1991 (Box 27)
  - Robinson, Lois, 1985-1992 (Box 27)
  - Rush, Florence, 1986-1993 (Box 27)
  - Rush – Best Kept Secret reviews, 1980 (Box 27)
  - Rush – C.V. (Box 27)
  - Rush – child pornography and ordinance, 1984 Nov. (Box 27)
  - Rush – civil rights, 1984 Oct. (Box 27)
  - Rush – perpetrators, 1984 Jan. 12 (Box 27)
  - Russell, Diana, 1985-1990 (Box 27)
  - Sadistic doctors, 1988 (Box 27)
  - Symposium on Media Violence and Pornography – proceedings, resource book, and research guide (Box 28)
  - Sadomasochism (Box 29)
  - S/M – porn and domination, Eva Kittay (Box 29)
  - Satanism, 1987-1991 (Box 29)
  - Satanism – occult seminar, 1990 Feb. 1 (Box 29)
  - Scott, David – summary of research in aggressive porn, 1984 (Box 29)
  - Scouten, Ellen Bradshaw, 1990 (Box 29)
  - Screw mag, Al Goldstein, 1987-1989 (Box 29)
  - Seattle conference, 1986 Nov. 1 (Box 29)
  - Seattle, 1990 (Box 29)
  - Sedgwick, Eve Kosofsky, 1988-1990 (Box 29)
  - Stanley Fish, 1992 Feb. (Box 29)
  - Self-defense/ Kathy Hopwood (Box 29)
  - Serial killer/ ripper, 1984-1999 (Box 29)
  - Sexual Assault Act of 1984 (Box 29)
  - Sex discrimination, 1986-1993 (Box 29)
  - Sex education, 1988-1996 (Box 29)
  - Sexual harassment, 1984-1996 (3 folders) (Box 29)
  - Sexual harassment workshop, 1989 Mar. 13 (Box 30)
  - Sex harassment – media portrayals (Box 30)
  - Sex harassment on college campuses, 1987-1988 (Box 30)
  - Sex offender castration, 1990 (Box 30)
  - Sign interpreting, 1985 (Box 30)
  - Shange, Notzake (Box 30)
  - Showers, Rob, 1986-1988 (Box 30)
  - Simonton, Ann (Box 30)
  - Skaggs/ Laura Lederer, 1987-1989 (Box 30)
  - Sisters Against Violence and Exploitation (S.A.V.E.) (Box 30)
  - S.A.V.E. handouts (Box 30)
  - Sisters of Justice, Women Take Liberty, 1986 Aug. (Box 30)
  - Southern Sisters Bookstore, 1988-1996, 6 of 7 folders (Box 30)
  - Southern Sisters Bookstore, 1988-1996, 7 of 7 folders (Box 31)
  - Southern Sisters store photos/ logo, 2 folders (Box 31)
  - Southern Sisters art exhibits – old (Box 31)
  - Smith, Linnea (Playboy), 1986-1995, 5 folders (Box 31)
  - Snuff (Box 31)
  - Speaking engagements – conferences, 1986-1987 (Box 31)
  - Speaking engagements – United Methodist Women of the North Carolina Conference, 1986 Oct. 3-4 (Box 31)
  - Speaking engagements – lesbian battering conference, San Francisco, 1987 May 2 (Box 31)
  - Speaking engagements, 1986-1987 (Box 31)
  - Spence, Terri (Box 32)
  - Sports Illustrated women's athletics (Box 32)
  - Stanford conference/ L. Pettigrew, 1987 Aug. 28-30 (Box 32)
  - Stanton, Therese (Box 32)
  - Stanton, Therese, 1994 (Box 32)
  - Spirituality, women's (Box 32)
  - Stats about porn (Box 32)
  - Status of women – Asian (Box 32)
  - Stock, Wendy (Box 32)
  - Stephenson, Marian (Box 32)
  - Stoltenberg, John, 1990-1994 (3 folders) (Box 32)
  - Student papers (Box 32)
  - Surveys on porn, 1986 (Box 32)
  - Swaggart, Jimmy, 1988 (Box 32)
  - Symposiums – conferences, general, 1987-1990 (Box 32)
  - Symposiums – Duke symposium, 1985 Jan. 11-12 (Box 32)
  - Symposiums – symposium contact letters (Box 32)
  - Symposiums – Duke symposium notes, 1985 (Box 33)
  - Symposiums – Duke symposium photographs, 1985 Jan. 11-12 [PHOTOGRAPHIC MATERIALS] (Box 33)
  - Symposiums – Duke Women's Studies symposium, 1989 Mar. 3-5 (Box 33)
  - Symposiums – Duke symposium evaluations, 1985 Jan. (Box 33)
  - Symposiums – NCCU symposium, 1985 Oct. (Box 33)
  - Symposiums – NCCU symposium evaluation, 1985 Oct. (Box 33)
  - Symposiums – Duke press kit, 1984 (Box 33)
  - Symposiums – NCCU press kit, 1985 (Box 33)
  - Take Back the Night, 1985-1988 (Box 33)
  - Teen pregnancy, 1985-1997 (Box 33)
  - Teen sex (Box 33)
  - Texas – Bronwyn Barakji (Box 33)
  - Thelma and Louise, 1991 (Box 33)
  - Tong, Rosemary, 1986 Fall (Box 33)
  - Toronto – CCAVE, 1984 Feb. 5 (Box 33)
  - Toronto symposium – handouts, 1984 Feb. (Box 34)
  - Toronto symposium – press coverage, 1984 Feb. (Box 34)
  - Toronto symposium – feminist statement, 1984 Feb. (Box 34)
  - Trebilcot, Joyce, 1989 June (Box 34)
  - Turlington, Patricia, 1985 (Box 34)
  - Turner, Alicia (Box 34)
  - University of N.C. Women's Studies, 1987-1989 (Box 34)
  - UNC – too many women enrolled, 1987-1989 (Box 34)
  - U.S. Department of Justice, 1988 Jan. (Box 34)
  - U.S. attorneys, 1985 Jan. (Box 34)
  - Vadas, Melinda (2 folders) (Box 34)
  - Vadas, Melinda – "Pornography and the Autonomy of Women" (Box 34)
  - Village Voice, 1980-1984 (Box 34)
  - VOICES, 1983-1991 (Box 34)
  - Video (Box 34)
  - Violence against women, 1991-1996 (Box 34)
  - W.A.P. (Women Against Pornography) conference, 1987 Apr. 4 (Box 34)
  - W.A.P. Memorial Day conference NY organizing (Box 35)
  - W.A.P. NY Sexual Liberals conference, 1987 Apr. 4 (Box 35)
  - [Posters removed to Oversize Materials.] (Box 35)
  - Trafficking conference (Box 35)
  - Trafficking in women conference, 1989 (Box 35)
  - Coalition on Trafficking in Women, 1988-1989 (Box 35)
  - W.A.P. – bibliography and facts, definitions (Box 35)
  - W.A.P. – high school slide script (Box 35)
  - W.A.P. – sex violence articles (Box 35)
  - W.A.P. newsletters (Box 35)
  - W.A.P. slide show adult script (2 folders) (Box 35)
  - W.A.P. – miscellaneous (Box 35)
  - W.A.P. general, 1987-1988 (Box 35)
  - W.A.P. trafficking in women proposal to Butler Family Foundation, 1988 (Box 35)
  - W.A.P. – Jayne Stamen case, 1988 Mar. (Box 35)
  - W.A.P. grant – child porn/ sex abuse, 1985 Dec. 15 (Box 35)
  - Waring, Marilyn (Box 35)
  - Warrior, Betsy (Box 35)
  - WHISPER (Women Hurt in Systems of Prostitution Engaged in Revolt), 1986-1995 (Box 35)
  - WHISPER – prostitution (Box 35)
  - White, Van, 1984 Sept. (Box 35)
  - Williams, Angie, N.C. State Technician (Box 35)
  - Women and sex (Box 35)
  - Williams, Patricia, 1988 (Box 35)
  - Windham, Mary, 1991-1993 (Box 35)
  - Women and the law, 1986 Mar. 20-23 (Box 35)
  - Women Against Sex (W.A.S.) – A Southern Women's Writing Collective (Box 35)
  - W.A.S. – Gayle Rubin – "Thinking Sex" (Box 36)
  - W.A.S. (Box 36)
  - W.A.S. speech – drafts (Box 36)
  - W.A.S. – questionnaires (Box 36)
  - Old W.A.S. speech drafts (Box 36)
  - Women fighting back, 1987-1999 (Box 36)
  - Women friendships, 1987 (Box 36)
  - Women honored and women's history (Box 36)
  - Women rising in resistance (Box 36)
  - Women's History Research Center, 1988-1995 (Box 36)
  - Women who kill, 1988-1995 (Box 36)
  - Women Organizing Against Pornography and Prostitution (Box 36)
  - Women in politics, 1986-1990 (Box 36)
  - Women political artists (Box 36)
  - Women in prison, 1998-1999 (Box 36)
  - Women – statistics on population (Box 36)
  - Women work and education, 1987-1991 (Box 36)
  - Women and work, 1986-1990 (Box 36)
  - Women's Review of Books (Box 36)